<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rs.xsl" ?>
<doc>
    <assembly>
        <name>MarcheGains</name>
        <version>1.0</version>
    </assembly>

    <requirements>

        <requirement name="F:Virtual_Bank_Account">
            <summary>
            The Custumer should be able to set up a virtual Bank account that holds values for money available to invest, and investments in each stock or mutual fund.
            </summary>
        </requirement>

      <requirement name="F:Bank_Account_Information">
        <summary>
          Holds Customers Bank Account information for final investment stage, that will be sent with investment information.
        </summary>
      </requirement>

        <requirement name="F:Personal_Investments">
            <summary>
            The Custumer should be able to see investments, whether they are going up or down. 
            </summary>
        </requirement>

        <requirement name="F:Personal_Investment_Trends">
            <summary>
            The Custumer should be able to graphically see personal trend of stock or mutual fund investment.
            </summary>
        </requirement>

        <requirement name="F:Personal_Investment_Recommendation">
            <summary>
             The Custumer should be able to view possible future daily trends
            </summary>
        </requirement>

        <requirement name="F:Statistics_Personal_Investment">
            <summary>
            The Custumer should be able to view statistics on stocks invested in over time of ownership.
            </summary>
        </requirement>
      
      <requirement name="F:Trend_Graphics">
        <summary>
          Graphical view of trends of owned stocks and other stocks.
        </summary>
      </requirement>

        <requirement name="F:General_Stock_Statistics">
            <summary>
           The Custumer should be able to view Statistics of all stocks individually over their life time.
            </summary>
        </requirement>

        <requirement name="F:Homepage_News">
            <summary>
            After log in the Custumer should be able to view current high and low stocks in the world. Stock Exchange opening time and closing times.
            </summary>
        </requirement>

        <requirement name="F:Investment_Process">
            <summary>
             Customer will enter this when he decides to make an investment and specifies the excact number of shares to purchase.
            </summary>
        </requirement>

      <requirement name="F:Investment_Preview">
        <summary>
          Customer will be able view the potential investments that he/she has made.
        </summary>
        </requirement>
      <requirement name="C:Operating System">
        <summary>
          This will be a Windows application only.
        </summary>
      </requirement>
      
        <requirement name="R:Checkout_Investment">
          <summary>
            Checking out will produce a file that will be sent to the investment firm with all necessary information to finilaize the purchase. This will also update current bank information and available funds.
          </summary>
        </requirement>

      <requirement name="R:API_Call">
        <summary>
          The Software has to be able to access the internet and the server of the API has to be running for any statistics or searches.
        </summary>
      </requirement>

    </requirements>
</doc>
